I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. It's all thanks to the Ninja
Creamy, or if you have the new machine,
the Ninja Swirl, which lets you make
soft serve or ice cream out of any
frozen liquid. Let me show you the seven
I made this week. The first one you saw
was an Oreo McFlurry. The second one was
a matcha soft serve. And now what you're
seeing is a Thai tea protein soft serve
topped with some sweet and condensed
milk. Oh my god, it was good. Now, this
is a double Oreo protein soft serve. So,
it's an Oreo flavored base topped with
some crushed Oreos. Absolutely dectable.
And now, this is a pineapple banana Dole
Whip with coconut milk. Super clean,
super healthy, and super easy. And now
this is just a cookie dough, vanilla
base topped with cookie dough pieces all
mixed in. Absolutely delicious. Always
hits the spot. And then to end it off,
we did a pink berry recreation of their
tart frozen yogurt. And this just hits
every single time.